And we live. Let's go.
>> What's up, Michelle?
>> How are you?
>> I'm doing great. They're just like
prompting
limited this time this week.
>> How many limits did you get this week?
>> Daily.
>> Yeah. Know like I I I think I could a
day with clothes and then poof.
>> Well, I think it was offline for like
three days in a row.
>> Yeah. And uh Yeah. I like limitation.
like 100% there is a bug like did you
see on the timeline like the GOS token
stuff where they added like more 20k
token in in system prompt that's nobody
knows where they are but they are
somewhere
>> yeah you see the tokens going out but
you see nothing in return and no
tracking where it went
>> well the [__] is going on
>> it it it's a bit like crypto right
>> all the fees going everywhere but you
don't know who's taking it
>> and Then you make like a 10x investment,
but at the end of the day, you lose
money anyway.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And then it just goes
offline and that's the end.
>> Yeah. Uh GM. Okay. Are we live? Looks
like it.
>> Yeah.
>> Was it just me? Because every time that
Claude had issues in the last days, it
always was at the end of the European
working day.
>> Yes. 4 to 5.
>> It's because there is like the peak
hours, right? So for us in it's in the
afternoon.
>> Mhm.
>> Um so I don't know what they're doing
like and the vibe coding code. So like
>> review the pull request, bro.
>> But even if it goes offline, we still
have the whole day.
>> Yeah. What?
>> We we have the entire day and just that
the last two hours goes offline. So,
>> I'm I'm I'm I'm woking up at 6 a.m.
>> Yeah.
>> Get like the levitation stuff.
>> Yeah. To make sure you're not in the
peak hours.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Which is kind of I don't
like that. But yeah, it is what it is.
I'm just checking. Yes. Good. Cool.
Okay. So, is it introduction time?
>> It is.
>> Let's go.
You want to do it?
>> Do we have the Do we have it somewhere?
>> Oh, yeah. It's It's like a boom. Like if
you This video is for you.
>> Yeah, I have it open. But
I don't see the introduction.
>> It's called open.
You don't like my vibe coded app?
>> I like it, but it doesn't show me. It
doesn't like me.
>> What? Okay. Am I refreshing? No, it's
working.
>> Wait.
>> Cold open.
>> Yeah, cold open. If you This video is
for you. That's the introduction.
>> Oh, the entire thing. All the blue
lights.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, but that's big.
>> Oh, okay. Should I do it?
>> It's no problem. I can put it in front
of me so it will look like I'm actually
thinking. Uh, the text is not that great
because it was used by Codex. So, yeah.
Yeah. Well, let's go.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's go. You do it.
>> Are we ready?
>> So, if you hate AI, this video is for
you because the bad news is it will take
parts of your job and in some cases the
whole job. And no, you are not going to
shame it out of existence.
While half of the internet is still
arguing about whether AI should even be
allowed to exist, the people using it
every day already know this is the most
powerful piece of technology and most of
us will see it in our lifetime.
We are using it every day and most of
the people screaming about it or not,
they are stupid.
Most anti-AII opinions are still coming
from people reacting to slop, theft,
anxiety, and culture war aesthetics
without ever spending serious time
inside cloud codecs or modern agent
workflows where the actual leverage is.
They are not wrong about the garbage.
They are wrong about the trajectory. The
point of view is emotional first,
aesthetic first, moral first. It is not
utilitarian and it's not grounded in
what these tools now do in the hands of
the people who actually use them like us
and you can riot against it if you want
and it is still going to happen and we
are going to show you why.
>> Boom.
So
>> it sounded like AI like crazy right like
[__]
>> Yeah.
Next time tell it to not put in so many
difficult words in
>> English. Yeah,
>> it's not my native language.
>> No, I don't think it's native language
of anyone, bro.
>> It's AI.
>> Yeah. And I
>> Yeah,
>> I think the conclusion is of the intro.
People hate it and the only people who
hate it are the ones not using it and
not billing the customers a lot for
doing only a small amount of work.
>> Yeah. I mean I when you see like the
entropic move about like limiting
subscription and like oh yeah by the way
peak hours uh and then if you use it
between 9 and 11 then you're going to
pay double or you're gonna use it double
blah blah blah but your weekly limits
are the same bro like that's kind of
like anti- user it's not user friendly
at all. No, but you let's say you have
the the biggest subscription $200
>> and you can build like 40 hours of work.
If you had that before AI and it was a
deaf, you would say, "Give me five of
those depths for $200 and I will just
keep on using it. So get a second
account and don't complain. Just use it
and make sure that you make the money."
>> Yeah. like everyone is sub subsidies
uh they put the the cost of the
customers right on the next customers.
So everyone is selling to customers of
the customers of the customers and then
you 10x the cost of production.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's true. So yeah, that
that could that could works on like one,
two, three levels, but yeah, maybe
that's just consulting business stuff
and everyone.
>> Yeah,
>> but still if you see what you can do
with it, just $200 for like eight hours
of views a day. That's perfect.
>> Oh, that's that's that's insane. What
What did you do this week with like all
of the prompt?
>> I did so much.
I I'm doing a lot with it. I think um I
don't know if my customers are watching
and I tell them, but I didn't touch any
code at all this year.
>> No, no. Yeah. Like
>> and it doesn't matter if it's if it's a
PHP Laravel project, if it's building
WordPress, if it's Python.
>> Yeah.
>> Everything I put in and I have some some
flows that check each other like Codex
Cloud, but yeah, the code is still
better than what I would do before. And
it's so much faster.
>> Yeah. Oh, it's just crazy. And
especially when you start combining like
Codex code together
like like your workflow with like the
planning stuff, it's powerful.
>> Yeah. Like
>> and before it's even the the most
easiest thing like a WordPress website,
>> people would install so many plugins,
buy them for like $50 a year and you
have a whole list and now customers come
to me because the website is slow and
cloud just rebuilds all the plugins to
custom plugins within an hour.
>> Mhm. and it optimizes the website and
they lose all the subscriptions, pay me
once and we proceed.
>> Have you seen the Shopify subscription
like the
uh Shopify integration of MCP?
>> Yeah, I didn't try it.
>> They say you can do the entire sale
optimization checking tracking
everything through the MCP.
>> Yeah. Uh yes. So here path
Shopify path
>> you have it active. Oh no no that's X.
>> Yes. Uh yeah. So that's Shopify in every
CLI.
>> Yeah.
>> Like that's that's crazy. And I think
that's the right way of doing like
selling a software or doing like an
application. That's that's the future of
like every SAS company out there.
>> Yeah. The only thing is here it says uh
now apply 50% discount on all of my
products.
>> Yes. All of my product.
>> Yeah.
>> I still don't know if I trust AI to just
optimize and change everything.
>> No, but that's a skill like
>> Yeah, I know. But still, do you trust
you have been building your web shop for
so long
>> and we are the ones using AI, but still
I would always just at least double
check everything it does.
>> How do you check like a Shopify with
like 15,000
products?
>> After this before I start, I always tell
it what you need to do is every change
you make, you write it down in a file in
a text file. So when I say you are going
to update every product uh create a text
file or put it in Excel and show me all
the differences so I can just easily
scroll over it and see the differences
and see if there are any weird things in
it.
>> Yeah, but that happened because um
I mean Okay, so I'm going to start that.
Uh no performance warning. I don't want
that. Where is it? [__] Okay, stop. Um,
it's because, yeah, it's because we are
like Opus and GH GPT 5.4, but you're
going to trust GPT7.
>> Oh, yeah. We we trust already Opus 4.6.
So,
>> I I pushed Clo to production server. I
mean, yeah, doing app stuff, right? and
it's still live
>> is but yeah I I didn't reach the scale
of like okay there is like one million
user on the like uh yeah I'm I'm not
managing YouTube right so if the AI is
do yeah I mean I'm migrating I I
migrated like a closed source uh project
to open source and then first commit it
leaked my production keys so
Yeah.
>> So you complain to Opus and say how
could you do that?
>> Why why did you committed?
>> Yeah.
>> Um I told you to be secure.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But like Mitos like how do
you trust Mitos to do the findings
security that we'll do in the next
uh couple of weeks, right?
>> Yeah. I think as soon as Mitos finds
more than you could do yourself, then
you trust it.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> that's all that needs to do is find a
few more than you can even do yourself.
>> Yeah. Oh, it's Yeah. So, for example,
like do you think like security
engineers will like scream against
methos because it's too powerful and
they don't have anything to do.
>> Oh yeah. I think for two reasons.
Because the first reason is they are
losing their jobs
and the second reason is they know how
fast it can go because they know how
security works and once you bypass a
small thing they understand how easy it
is to leak a full database of data.
>> Yeah.
>> So they are the ones saying that when is
leaked into the wrong hands of people
abusing it using it for bad behavior for
hacking and everything.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, who's going to stop them?
>> Who's going to stop? Anyone?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Mitos was a bit like that was
honestly during our live stream when I
saw like the benchmark and stuff. Uh I
was okay. Uh that's that's the Pandora
box like like it for even for me I felt
it was the Pandora box moment.
Like like the guy who said, "Yeah, okay.
I found a bug in a 30 years old codebase
like OpenBSD server blah blah blah and I
can be admin on every [__] open BSD
server on earth
>> bro.
>> Yeah, but it's not even in your code
just the the operating system that's
running on a VPS or whatever.
>> Everything can be hacked and then even
if your app is fully secure,
>> you still have a problem.
>> You're never fully secure anyway, right?
And and then you we will have Mitos 1.5
and Mitos 2.0.
>> Yeah. And what are you going to tell
your customer every time? Oh no, it's
AI. I can do anything about it.
>> Yeah. I mean like the solution of AI
attacks or AI defenders
like we need MTOS 2 before like the
North Korean are using MTOS 1.5. So, do
you think there will be like an AI
Cloudflare that you put in front of your
website and that's not a firewall like
Cloudflare but just a full AI firewall?
>> Yeah. Like 100% that's the that's the
job of Cloudflare.
>> Yeah.
>> Like I would I don't want to be a
CloudFare engineer right now because
then you need to fight North Korean
hackers
>> or even everyone with a MTO CLI.
Yeah,
>> good luck with that.
>> Well, let's see. Uh, did they already
tell besides the big companies like
Microsoft and everything, what company
is going to get access?
>> No, like I think it's limited and like
like what who the [__] do you know
what's going on behind closed door,
right?
>> No, you never know.
>> Yeah. But yeah, so there is like
security aspect of it and uh Okay. So
what about what's your point of view
about the artist like saying uh yeah
they stole my work and uh it's not AI
art AI prompting is not art like do you
understand the backlash?
>> Yeah. They say they trained on my data
on my on my art and now it's using my
techniques to create new art for other
people.
>> Yeah.
But man, is that is that legit? It's
like, bro. Okay, so I have an example
here. Uh
>> yeah, I can say something that will make
them all angry.
>> You are complaining about art. Something
that takes you so much time while AI
gives you so many opportunities. Go make
money.
>> Yeah, I know. Exactly. Uh okay. Wait,
wait, wait. You got to say that again so
I can have you I would put you on
say it again.
Well, yeah, eventually AI will steal it
and not even steal it, it will just copy
it, create something, but even if it
does it by itself and it goes through
the same steps as you have done, it will
come to the same result. That's
possible. So, don't complain. Just go
and earn money with AI because of so
many opportunities that you get. Be
creative and use AI to go even further.
>> Yeah. And I like
>> Yeah. people can uh
uh sell like humanmade art anyway.
>> Yeah,
>> you will have you will have like 1
million piece of AI art and then you
will have one painting where you spend
20,000 uh hours on it
>> and people will pay for it. There's no
because they want the personal stuff.
>> But
>> but we are not complaining that we lost
our jobs. I mean, no, we didn't.
Did we?
>> Well, if we if we didn't change
anything, we would have lost our entire
job.
>> Like I mean like I upgrade all of my npm
package every day.
>> Yeah.
>> Like I have to upgrade my skills every
day too, right? Like it's
>> you go from one stack to another. Like I
I don't understand why a developer would
be against AI two years ago. Evan
because it's it's like
>> Stack Overflow died because of AI but
before AI we were copy pasting [__] from
Stack Overflow.
>> Yeah.
>> Like it's just a [__]
>> So it's all about continuing and
adapting new techniques.
>> Yeah. No, exactly. And if you want if
you are a builder like if you want to
code because like we spend hours
configuring AI uh and scripting and
configuration. Anyway, it's part of the
job anyway, right? Like, yeah, you don't
write code. You don't copy paste
>> like
>> codes to put here to put that and then
create a the one million time of CRUD
dashboard for Shopify e-commerce or like
SAS apps or whatever like
>> it's not a oneclick solution.
>> Uh yeah, and so yeah, just like back to
the art uh I'm going to put screen.
Yeah. Okay, cool. So fantasy artist Greg
Rutoski image was scrapped the most out
of the any artist across all generative
AI site. Rutoski was not happy and made
vocal opposition of AI generated art. As
a result, his art was removed from
training data set of the diffusion 2.0.
However, Gen AI user developed tools
like Laura to bypass the new stable
diffusion restriction.
It was uh yeah one year ago, right?
um to mimic the net is is now filled
with AI rtosk ripoff and kind of like
what we saw with the studio gibli with
JGBT, right?
>> Yes.
>> You put limitation in a a closed model
then you will have opensource models
that will do exactly the same [__]
thing. So it's that's it. It's open. And
I mean, yeah, that looks like an
illustration that you can prompt on uh
Nano2 like in 5 seconds.
>> I would just say you're an artist. Be
creative and turn it around and make
money on it. Tell people that's based on
your art and they can can even get an
original one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Like Yeah. Instead
of having like a pictures on your
computer, get instead of having an NFT,
uh just buy the real painting. Exactly.
>> So yeah,
is do you think AI gen is art anyway?
Cuz it can be beautiful, right?
>> It can be much better than stuff that
people make themselves.
>> Exactly. But it is so normally when you
had an artist to do something for you,
even if it was a website or whatever,
then
you would just ask a question and hope
that it's correct. And if you need any
changes, you have to wait like a week or
two.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> And that's all gone. You can just prompt
whatever you need within a day. But
that is more for use cases and
everything. So, if you want real art
that you hang on the wall, I would still
do something that an artist created and
not do it on on an AI. But for
everything else that I need for us that
I want to change myself, AI is so much
better.
>> Yeah. I mean, and do you care about how
it's made? Like for example, if tomorrow
you watch a AI movie fully generated by
AI by on Netflix like Netflix quality
movie stuff.
>> Yeah. Exactly.
>> But still it's the same question. Do you
care how uh software is made, developed
by me or by an AI?
>> Exactly. Like Yeah. Who cares? Like I'm
I'm output maximalist.
>> Yeah. And I still think that a lot of
directors and everything can create
Netflix movies. Yes.
>> Quality with AI, but they can put in
such a cool story and do whatever they
want.
>> Exactly.
>> Why do you need to put in a million
dollar actor? Yeah. Yeah. 100%. And like
I I don't understand like the I mean
there is beauty in like mastering a form
of art, right? and spending like hours
and hours on doing something. But it,
you know, it's like um you're going to
commission
a graphic designer to make a logo and
you expect him to spend days on it to
have a beautiful logo and then it he it
will do the logo of Nike, right?
>> And then it took like five five seconds
to just swipe it and have one of the
best logo of the industry. But it also
like uh but you you want your graphic
designer to spend days on your logo
>> just because
>> I do it differently now. I just prompt
like 50 logos on something that I want
in G.
>> Yeah.
>> And I compare them all and then I give
them to a graphic designer. I say hey
here are three examples of what I want.
This is how I want it.
Can you make it for me in a bit more
creative way?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And even for us,
right, like as a developer, you can be
hired uh by someone who already has a
MVP and you take out like the vibe coded
version of the app and uh you build
something sustainable instead of one
more side project that's going to die
tomorrow, right? Like it's more
exciting.
>> Yeah.
>> So yeah, it's I don't get it. And same
thing like for the I was listening a
podcast about music and the guy was
producer uh for the last 20 years and
then he tried Suno.
>> Mhm.
>> And he got a mixed from Suno and he said
um I could have made that
reached the quality of my craft after 20
years of um
of doing it like every day of my life
for 20 years. And now Suno can like
didn't just like not not really prompt
like one shot prompted it but uh after a
couple of hours Suno reach the same
point of me right.
>> Yeah.
>> But also you had I don't know I read it
somewhere but that guy who made AI music
put it on Spotify and then he had so
many AIs listening to it.
>> Yeah. I think that's weird
because you have AI listening to it just
for your own gain and making money and
you're using so many resources spamming
Spotify with so much music. I don't
think that's correct. But if you make
good AI music and you earn money
>> because so many people are actually
listening to it
>> then they like the music. So who cares
what made it?
>> Yeah. Oh, exactly. But the the thing is
like okay so you will have like 1
million AI music generated every day.
How do you get like discovered by a
human which is I mean you can have an
agent that will give you music that you
like.
>> Yeah.
>> I I think like yeah I think everyone
will have their own agent based on their
memory MD file and you will get what you
want. But is this not the point where
you come into real life people who are
like influencers? Because agents need to
find
>> something that you like. So most of the
time you just give up so many
influencers who produce music that you
like and find something similar. Yeah.
>> So then you're back to not creating
music, but doing it in a different way
and being creative to make sure that
your music gets out through certain
connections to people and you don't get
those connections with AI. You have to
make them yourself.
>> Oh, okay. Wait, like you're saying like
you don't have like the human connection
from the music.
>> No, I'm saying that creating the music
can be done by AI.
>> Yeah. But to promote it and get it into
the correct platforms, you have to you
need to have social contacts,
>> you need to to to make your network
bigger, go to events, talk to people,
and then share what you have
>> to make sure that your AI music goes
further because if it lands on the pile
of 10 million songs, who is going to
notice it? But that's what I'm saying
like everyone has their own agent based
on their preference and stuff and then
the agent will build for yourself your
own timeline for example like you own
Spotify.
>> Yeah.
>> But that's the thing is okay you don't
need to find music. If you have that
then your agent can build the music you
want to listen.
>> Well that's the next step.
And yeah, and yeah, that Oh, yeah. That
that would be interesting. Like, yeah.
Do you really want to listen to the next
uh Katy Perry song or do you want to
make something that sounds like
and then you get the same emotion from
it or whatever.
>> Get emotion from Katy. I don't know.
>> People who go to music events, they want
to share with other people. So, you need
to all listen to the same song.
>> That's true. Same thing like if you get
a Netflix generated movie just for you,
you can talk about it with your friend
on internet.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah. So yeah, like culture will be
interesting, right? Because
which common culture do you have when
your AI generated content for you?
>> Yeah.
But this also shows how many
opportunities there are
>> 100%
>> and nobody can
>> predict where it's going
>> 100% like because yeah like again like
what if you connect on X and you only
see twe that will be interesting to you
and your timeline is AI generated
>> I think that's much better
>> yeah exactly because because by
definition it will be be based on your
preferences right so
hm M
>> but then you even don't mind ads because
ads are based on your preferences.
>> Exactly. Yeah. You get targeted. Yeah.
So then it's like just sponsored slash
highly targeted
content.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And even like um like for example
for us like no we don't have followers
on YouTube yet like if you subscribe to
the channel.
>> Yeah. All of the view that we get right
now it's because YouTube algo
recommended to the viewers right. So we
produce the content it get recommended
to people.
We could AI generated everything and
YouTube could recommen recommend like uh
content not even human generated or
generate a video to get the viewers to
watch a video about a search or you can
search something on YouTube and the
video that uh you want to watch is
generated on the fly.
>> Yeah, that's cool. Yeah,
>> but that's like giving everybody a
unique video.
>> Yeah, but like for examp like for
example, if I want to watch a cooking
video
uh on YouTube, like I say, which recipe
can I do with my fridge, like the the
stuff I have in my fridge, you take a
picture of your fridge, you go on
YouTube, bam, video of like cooking
something recipe, blah blah blah.
And like it's so exciting. Oh yeah.
>> This is how how much you can do with it.
So there is so much I don't even know
where to start.
>> Yeah. Now it's just not because Okay.
Like even like you you can't really say
okay I want the YouTuber to have made
this recipe for me like six months ago
and then the algo find find it for me
because I search for it.
>> No. No. It's easier to just generate as
you ask.
>> Exactly.
So yeah, it's and even like content like
ads the ads industry will be like yeah
you have ads on the fly.
>> Yeah. But you can adjust the ads based
on the content that the person is
looking at or is reading.
>> Yeah. Or even like talk about in the
convers. How cool is that?
>> Yeah. It's it's and it's so exciting but
still like look uh I got a studies here
>> where you have okay so it was in so
March okay so it was uh last month 50%
of the American are more concerned than
excited about the increased use of AI in
daily life uh percent of who said the
increase use of artificial intelligence
in their life make them feel more
concerned than excited 37% in 21 and
right now we have 50%. Equally excited
or concerned 38 okay thank you more
excited than concerned 10% 10% only of
the US guy
>> they are supposed to be like pioneers of
technology or whatever and probably like
10% it's just California silicode valley
guy
>> yeah just a small group of people well
the other question is the 50% who are
more concerned do they even know how
much is AI already
because Almost every company is using
it, integrating it, using it to
optimize, to read data faster, to to
make it more personalized for you and
they don't even know.
>> Yeah. But are they really using it
though like you know
>> they are not actively using it but
passively
because the if you use Google now the
first result is always AI.
>> Yeah. No, like Google page is insane
like
>> and it's it's good. It always has a
correct result.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, for example, Okay. Like
uh so I
I run I Okay. So, it's news related.
It's politics. So, it's AI news. Uh AI
mode. Yeah. It's going to be a
conversation. Uh so yeah there is no
generated
>> ask the question
>> Spotify uh which but uh whatifi
released recently
I have view okay so mid
>> physical book sales page match audio
book okay whatever whatever so that's
generated I expected okay I expected
more ads oh no I want brave So we don't
see the ads.
>> Yeah, but the ads don't matter. It's
about about the first thing AI overview.
>> Yeah,
>> I'm really sure most people just read
the result and they are not even going
to the AI mode%
>> but they are using this and to me every
time I use it this is spot on.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. So that means
like okay so you have the AI generated
search on Google and then you have like
some sponsor link that we don't see here
and then
>> um like at the bottom of the page you
start to have u the first organic result
like SEO oriented stuff. Nobody's going
to see Spotify uh new releases on that
page when I'm not on Brave because it's
AI overview stuff. Yeah.
>> Like, yeah, that's it's crazy. Um,
I mean, I can't wait for the ads
industry to die, honestly. Like,
>> it will be different.
>> Yeah. And I mean, like having ads in
open like chat GPT interface, I I find
that lazy as [__] Like putting ads in a
conversation chat, it's lazy. I don't
know. Like
>> Yeah. Well, I still think as soon as it
comes out because right now it's Spotify
off Spotify, Shopify was going to allow
you to sell your products to through Jed
GPT.
>> But I think it's only going to be in in
the US first. So, it's not in the EU
yet, but once it is, I'm going to try it
ASAP.
>> Yeah. But I mean, like
>> it feels like the first Facebook days.
Yeah. where you could just spend a few
cents and get new customers.
>> I don't think it will be a few cent
though. Like
>> they know what they can charge but
>> Yeah. No, exactly. Like the the
OpenAI ads platform will not be like
Google ads platform when they they're
going to try to find the pricing like
they have an idea of what they can
charge pay click for sure. But what I
would have done with or what I would
have do if I was like a
instead of the ads you take a commission
of every transaction that goes to stripe
via stripe via charg.
>> Mhm.
>> Like if the origin is charg like half a
percent or 0.01% of the transaction and
it goes to chip.
>> Yeah. It might be it might even be
possible that they already are going to
do it.
>> True. But like having a [__] block of
because you're going to lose the trust
of the conversation of why Chip told you
to buy that pro like to choose this
product when you ask which one is better
because they will have had running on
that product you know so
yeah we'll see it goes
uh okay so who's not happy about AI
>> well who else
>> so many people.
>> Yeah,
>> a lot of anti still come from besping
today. Yes. Okay. So, yeah. So, um a lot
of AI haters are coming from chat GPT
3.5, right? But yeah, again, they didn't
talk like they never they can't even pro
imagine what we can do with like code uh
4.6. Yeah, it's like buying a car for
€1,000 and then complaining that racing
cars is impossible.
>> Yeah. No, it's it's nano nano2, right?
Like when you prompt an image where you
can create a full marketing campaign
with like five prompt, that's just
crazy.
>> Yeah, they are still used to when you
when you prompt a person, it has seven
fingers. Yeah, know exactly like Yeah,
it's just crazy. Like, okay, so you
scroll on TikTok, you only see AI slop
stuff, right? Like AI generated content,
not AI slop. AI slop for me is like
trash content. AI content can be good
content.
>> Yeah, but you have to spend time on it
to creating it. You can't just do one
prompt and and create a thousand ads
>> with Yeah, of course it's possible. But
if you spend a little bit more time,
>> yeah,
>> it will be so much better.
>> Yeah. No, no, 100%. Like the but even
like from one month to another like the
quality of output AI generated is like
10 times better. Um but yeah again like
uh 90% of the AI generated content is
like pure SL but 10% is 10 times better
than human output right um so yeah good
at the end of the day like good content
is good content for me it's like okay uh
this image has been photoshopped I don't
like it.
>> Yeah
>> like what the [__] are you talking
about? Yeah, but just give it a few more
months and people won't see the
difference. Right now, if you have the
really good models, you already don't
see a difference between AI and a real
image. Like people are saying, "Yeah, we
need a label. We need to force people
tagging if it's AI generated."
>> Yeah.
>> When 70% of the content on internet is
AI generated, like what the [__] are you
talking about?
>> Yeah. And they are not going to do it. I
mean on YouTube like if the video is AI
generated you need to tag it and on the
uh on Instagram too like if the like the
some of the AI influencer I have on
Instagram um I need to say that the
image is AI generated and then I get
like some DM from fan view
influencers that say oh yeah you want to
create an account here
>> yeah it's an upsell
>> yeah no upsell so But again, like uh
yeah, a girl on Instagram with like big
boobs and like bikinis will make more
views than ugly real girl.
>> Yeah. And I don't think people mind that
it's AI. They just keep on scrolling.
>> I mean, when you when you see the the
the impression of those like AI
generated uh models, no, people don't
give a [__] about
>> No, they don't.
>> Yeah. Oh, for sure. Um, so yeah. Okay.
So even
people will also complain about uh the
the resources of AI like oh yeah we are
we don't have enough energy
um it's it's consuming like too much and
stuff like
>> yeah well if we don't if we don't do it
other people will you don't have a
choice it's here
>> yeah like
all of the problem that AI has right now
because yeah there is like some of it
like people like committed suicide
because yeah they got like pushed by an
AI chat right to whatever. Um so yeah
there is some guwell to have in place
for sure but um like AI will be the
solution of all of the problem that it
will pose. Yeah. And it will create some
more problems. And
>> wait, I I'm just convinced there's
nothing you can do about it. Learn to
live with it.
>> Yeah.
>> Take profit of it and you can complain,
but do it like for a day and then just
see what you can improve using it.
>> Yeah. I mean like you know for sure like
uh it's it's so powerful and there is so
so much money on the table that anyway
you can't stop it like like it's too
big. It's It's like stopping the [__]
like train after Oh, yeah. It's going
too fast.
>> Yeah.
>> Impossible.
>> Like Ellen Musk is going to put like
data center in space so we can have
space travel and like sending robots to
Mars because he can.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. For sure. And he needs
to.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Or are you going to send like 300 people
at once to Mars?
Yeah. And like he said, "Oh yeah, Nvidia
can't uh can't can give us the chips
that we need. So we're going to make
them and we're going to make them in
space." Okay, bro. I'm going to make
like videos on internet.
>> But what he does is next level.
>> Yeah. Like Yeah. That's crazy. And how
you are not excited by a guys who's
going to say before the IPO, so he say,
"Okay, yeah, we're going to do that.
we're going to space uh like tomorrow
because uh now the day after tomorrow
because tomorrow I have to to have the
biggest IPO ever. So there is that
right. But um yeah he said that he's
going to generate like twice the uh
terabyte of energy
than the US. Well, every normally a lot
of people say it and you don't believe
it, but it looks like he does everything
he says.
>> Yeah,
it was terra fab.
>> right.
>> And he just built another company in the
spare five minutes that he has left in
the week.
>> And and we are here walking on like
>> Yeah. Shopify
and in the same time that we spend on
logging in he has launched another
company doing something amazing.
Uh, tech. Okay. So, yeah. Terrafab, join
us on a journey. We aspire aspire to be
a galactic civilization. That's a
landing page, bro. That That's good.
That's good.
Uh, type one harness all of the energy
on the planet. Type two, the energy from
a star. Okay. The sun. Type three
harness all of the energy in a galaxy.
So, it wants to go to type two.
Whatever. Whatever.
>> Yeah. It's like
>> we are builders. No [__] bro.
Um, okay. Scaling the Starship V3 and
that's what he wants to put to space to
generate like energy. Okay. Okay.
Whatever. Yes. See terapab 0.5 terowatty
current annual US consumption.
It wants to do that per year uh twice.
>> Yeah. with that. I think I think it was
that or at least with that I broke and
he got the cars, he got the robots, he
got the the energy and then he got like
the rocket ship like thank and thanks to
XAI kind of like uh that's the that's
the brain.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Everything is powered by AI.
>> Yeah. Like how do you not getting
excited by that?
>> I don't think people even understand
what he's doing.
I mean, I understand that they want to
send big [__] to space.
>> Yeah. To get more energy and then that's
it. Because if you can produce twice the
energy of the US
>> Mhm.
>> Uh energy is not a problem anymore.
>> No.
>> What a [__]
>> Yeah. Well, that solves a lot of [__]
>> Yeah.
It's always sun in space.
>> That's the best slogan. Why are you
doing it? It's always sunny.
>> Uh the space the only truly scalable
solution for the future of AI. Boom.
Boom.
Uh like it's the next step. Luna mass
driver. Let's go. Let's go. But yeah,
like because of the the like the
technology advancement of the last 10
years, 20 years and even like since GPT
is 3.5, whatever, we can do that. Like
that's cool.
>> I like that.
>> But first, let's ask him if he can make
Grock available through CLI so we can
use it for coding.
>> Yeah, there is. I mean, Grock is not
that great neither. Like it's kind of
like [__] Yeah, I don't use it that
much. It's It's too hard to just use it
or too expensive.
>> Yeah, but for engagement it's quite
good.
>> It is.
>> Yeah. Like if you tag Gro under like a
tweet and stuff like a lot of people
like using it for engagement. So,
>> but you don't need to be cheap. You need
to have a higher subscription.
>> Yeah.
So, yeah. Um,
should we wrap it up?
>> Yes. So, what are we going to say? Let
the haters hate and we will just use it.
>> Yeah. Uh okay. Wait, what was the uh
>> what was the conclusion
>> made by AI?
>> Yes. Uh anti chron is mostly right.
Aesthetic. No, I don't want that. Uh
what does it mean for indie Dave this
week? Oh yeah, that's something.
>> You have to hot take.
>> Hot take. Why did I put the hot take?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Uh people make a okay.
So antiro is mostly right about the
aesthetic still wrong about the
trajectory. Oh, is that not something we
said in the introduction?
>> Yeah. Well,
then AI is stupid. But
>> I mean, yeah, I I need to rewrite the
skill for to generate a better.
>> Okay. But I mean, yeah, like again, AI
is too like 100% too big to fail. It's
not because you will have like a riot in
France or whatever like 15,000
people like rioting about oh yeah know
we don't want self-driving cars or we
don't want AI generated images on
internet
we're going to make billion of them. So
>> you better get used to it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Get used to it before like
your kids are scrolling Tik Tok with AI
generated content.
>> Yeah. Well, maybe it's a generation
issue.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> In 30 years, no. But we are the last
people knowing how everything works
without AI.
>> Yeah.
>> No, like when kids are like getting
brain rotated on Tik Tok by like the
banana fruit stuff generated like uh
Yeah. In in yeah, in 10 years, nobody
will care about like if it's a because
everything will be a generated anyways.
>> Yes. Oh yeah, you can riot. You can hate
AI, but you're going to lose. I
subscribe to the channel.
>> Thank you.
>> Bye.
Uh, end stream. Peace.